volgistics.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy | Volgistics

Your privacy is very important to us, and we carefully protect the information you manage through Volgistics. This privacy policy explains what information we collect, how we use it, and the measures we take to protect it. If, after reviewing this policy, you have additional questions, please contact the Volgistics team.

### What information we collect and how we use it

In order to use Volgistics, we ask you to provide your name, title, and email address, and the name and address of your organization. We collect this information when you initially sign-up for a free Volgistics trial account. If you choose to turn your trial account into a paid Volgistics account, we also ask for the email address of the person responsible for your account's payment arrangements, and your payment information and billing address.

We use this information as the basis for identifying you as the owner of the data you track in the system. We use your payment information to process your payment of service fees, and we use your billing contact's email address if we need assistance processing a payment. We may use your email address, or the email address of others you identify as 'Volgistics administrators' to communicate with you about the status of your Volgistics account.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide information about you, your volunteers or your organization to others for any reason. This includes personal information such as your name, address, or email address, and the name and address of your organization.

From time to time we may release collective statistics about the Volgistics system, such as the average number of volunteers organizations track, or the percentage of Volgistics Customers who fall into general organization classifications. These aggregate statistics never reveal information identifiable as that of an individual Customer.

### Who can access your information

Only people you identify as 'system operators' in your Volgistics account, and who you give access to 'Setup' can view or change your organization information (see also "What can Volgistics access" below). You view or change your organization information under 'Account management' in the Setup area.

Once you initially enter payment information for your account, no one can see your complete credit card or bank account number in Volgistics. Volgistics displays only the last four digits of these numbers, and only where it is necessary for you to identify the card or account used to pay for your service. (see also "What can Volgistics access" below).

### About the information you store in your Volgistics database

Your database includes all of the volunteer, coordinator, and assignment information you enter in your account, as well as all records related to those, including service records, history records, and contact records.

The information you store in your database belongs solely to you, and Volgistics carefully safeguards the privacy and security of this data. Volgistics never discloses the content of your database to anyone. Volgistics uses procedural and technical safeguards to protect your database against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access, including encryption, firewalls, and Secure Socket Layers. All data is stored in a secure data center. Volgistics uses many different security techniques to protect your data from unauthorized access by users internal and external, however it must be recognized that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

### What happens to your information if you close your account

We will continue to protect your information under the terms of this privacy policy even if you close your Volgistics account. If you cancel your Volgistics account, we delete your account information from our system within 30 days. If you allow your account to be automatically cancelled due to lack of payment, your account will first be put on a Hold status for 30 days beyond your Paid Through date and will be deleted 30 days after the Hold period expires. Trial accounts will be deleted 60 days after the trial account expires.

### Who can access the information you store in your Volgistics database

Access to the information you store in your database is carefully controlled through a three part credentialing system. This includes an account number, login name, and password. People you allow to access the system by giving them credentials are known as 'system operators.' Only people you authorize as system operators have online access to your database.

The person who initially signs-up for your trial account chooses a login name and password at the time they sign-up, becoming your organization's first system operator. Thereafter, that individual may create additional system operators for your account, and authorize others to use the system by providing them with system operator credentials. You can see who the current system operators are for your account at any time under 'System Operators' in the Setup area.

Only system operators in your organization with access to the setup page can create system operator credentials for your account. You are responsible for all actions taken with your Volgistics system operator credentials. Give system operator credentials only to those you wish to have access to your database. If you know or suspect that a system operator's credentials have been compromised, you should disable that system operator's access to the system immediately under 'System Operators' in the Setup area.

### What can Volgistics access?

In the course of managing the database, managing file system components and creating and testing system enhancements, authorized Volgistics developers will have access to the database. Volgistics customer service employees will have access to customer data as needed for the purpose of answering customer support inquiries. Volgistics employees may also access the 'event log' for your account for the purpose of answering your support inquiries or assisting you with system operation issues. This log contains a record of system setting changes, system errors, and related system events. You can view the event log for your account under 'Account management' in the Setup area.

The Volgistics accounting staff can only see part of your credit card information. The complete card number is not viewable.

The security of your data is extremely important to us and therefore all Volgistics staff work under strict Nondisclosure, Non-Competition and Non-Solicitation agreements and this Privacy Policy. In addition, all employees are subject to pre-employment and periodic background checks.

### Changes to this policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a notification of amended terms on the Welcome screen you view when you access your account. All amended terms will automatically become effective ten (10) days after they are posted on the Site. By using the Software or the Services after such revised terms are posted, you agree to be bound by any such amended provisions. Therefore, you agree to periodically visit the Site to examine the then-current Agreement.
